lolewomen.com 2019-05-09

# Privacy Policy – Lolë

**Last modified: July 27 th, 2017**

Please read carefully this Privacy Policy before visiting Coalision’s website at the following URL: [www.lolelife.com](http://www.lolewomen.com/)  (the “Site”)

### Coalision's commitment to privacy

Protecting your privacy is important to us and we recognize that your personal information must be used responsibly.

Our privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes the types of personal and non-personal information that Coalision Inc. ("Coalision") collects in relation to the operation of the Site, how we use such information and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it, and how you can access and modify collected information.

By using the Site, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site.

### What information is collected?

When you are just a visitor, Coalision does not collect any of your personal data, except when using cookies.

Coalision only collects personal information when you choose to: (i) contact us (ii) register on the Site (iii) complete a profile (iv) subscribe to newsletters (v) participate in a contest or to an event (vi) provide feedback or request information (vii) order products and services.

The personal information that Coalision collects through our Site may include your name, username, password, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number and any other personal information that you choose to include in your profile or requests. We collect this type of information in obvious ways through accurately-labeled forms and input fields.

As part of the standard operation of the Site, we may collect certain non-personal information from you, including but not limited to your browser type, operating system, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed the Site. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time you visit the Site, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing the Site, the number of times you return to the Site, the websites that you visit before or after you visit our Site and other click-stream data. This information helps us to improve our Site, respond to your requests and customize your shopping experience.

We may use cookies to collect the non-personal information described above. A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the Site. We may also use cookies to: (1) provide you with customized content and advertising; (2) monitor Site usage; and (3) conduct research to improve our content and services. You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Site or take full advantage of all our offerings. Check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

### How We Use Your Information

The information we collect allows us to keep you posted on Coalision’s latest announcements and upcoming events. From time to time, we may send you information on programs and services that we believe may be of interest to you.

If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can simply unsubscribe by clicking the “UNSUBSCRIBE” link at the bottom of a marketing email that you receive from Coalision or by contacting our customer service representatives at [customerservice@coalision.com](mailto:customerservice@coalision.com) or at 1-800-360-6724 option 5, Monday to Friday from 9AM to 5PM Eastern Time.

We also use information we collect to help us develop, deliver, improve and provide you with our best services, content and communications. We may use this information to complete any orders or fulfill any order requests, including enabling investigations of products.

We may use your information to send important notices or communications regarding your orders, even if you have opted out from our marketing communications.

We may use your information to fulfill any subscription requests, send you an e-mail confirming your subscription, and from time to time send you information for informing you of any change or additions to any subscriptions.

We may also use information we collect for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications.

We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information (i.e., data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual) for any purpose.

### How we share your information

You can choose which, if any, of our online resources you wish to participate in.

Coalision only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Coalision in the following limited circumstances:

We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for processing or fulfilling any orders on our behalf, or providing other services on our behalf, including marketing, support services, website services, delivering materials, answering customer questions. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Coalision will only provide these parties with the personal information they need to deliver the services to us and/or on our behalf.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of others as required or permitted by law, (e) as part of any merger, acquisition, financing, sale of company assets or interests in the company, or transition of service to another provider, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, or (f) if we believe such disclosure is necessary to identify, contract or bring legal action regarding injury or interference with the rights and property of Coalision.

### Social Media

The use of social networks in connection with Coalision’s Site may lead to the collection and exchange of some personal data between Coalision and such social network. We invite you to read the Privacy Policy posted on social media websites to be aware of what personal data can be transmitted to Coalision as well as the purposes of use, disclosure and retention of your personal data by such social media, in particular for advertising purposes. You can directly configure and control the access to and confidentiality of your personal data. Coalision shall not be responsible for any use of your personal data by social networks on their account.

### Intellectual Property

The content of our Site, including, but not limited to, trademarks, graphics, images, texts, videos, animations, sounds, logos, gifs and icons, and their formatting are the exclusive property of Coalision, except for trademarks, logos, or content belonging to third parties and authors.

Any reproduction, distribution, modification, adaptation, transmission or publication of these elements, even partial, is strictly prohibited without the express consent of Coalision and any of such undertaken by any process whatsoever constitutes an infringement punishable by applicable laws and regulations.

Failure to comply with these provisions constitutes an infraction which could result in civil and criminal penalties. Owners of any content may take legal actions against you.  Nothing on our Site shall be construed as conferring any right, title, interest or any other licence on our Site, its content, features or any material downloaded from the Site.

### Hyperlinks to third-party websites

There may be cases on our Site where Coalision provides hyperlinks to other websites or resources available on the Internet. Coalision has no control on such externally linked websites or webpage. Coalision shall not be deemed to endorse or guarantee such third website services. Coalision is not in any way responsible for any kind of damages or loss, arising out or in connection such external sources, including for the services or products they provide, or any use thereof. You are responsible for accessing such external sources and you must comply with their Terms of Use.

Users, subscribers and visitors to our Site must always obtain the prior written approval of Coalision before creating a hyperlink to our Site. Coalision reserves its right to accept or refuse any use of a hyperlink at its discretion.

### Hyperlinks to our Site.

Users of our Site authorized by Coalision may set up a hyperlink only to the Site’s homepage accessible at the following URL: www.lolelife.com, and only to the extent the webpage opens in a new window. No “framing” or “deep-linking” of our web pages or content is allowed. You agree to remove any hyperlink you may have set up upon request by Coalision.

### Protection of your information

To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and facilitate the appropriate use of information, Coalision uses physical, technological and administrative procedures to attempt to protect the integrity of its Site and the confidentiality of the data collected through the Site. Nevertheless, Internet transmissions are never completely private or secure. Coalision cannot be liable for any breaches of confidentiality due to system failures or unauthorized access by third parties.

### Protection of Children’s Personal Information

Coalision is concerned about protecting the safety and privacy of children. We do not knowingly or specifically request or collect personal information from or about children under thirteen and do not market specifically to children. We do, however, sell children’s products for purchase by adults.

### Access to Information You Provide to Us

You may access any personal information you provide to us, correct or modify any such personal information, or direct us to make no further use of your personal information. To do so, please send an email with your request to [customerservice@coalision.com](mailto:customerservice@coalision.com) or at 1-800-360-6724 option 5, Monday to Friday from 9AM to 5PM Eastern Time.

### Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy

The use of this Site constitutes the user's acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Site. Coalision reserves the right, in our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice.

### Questions or Comments

Coalision is open to questions and comments about this Privacy Policy. You can reach our customer service representatives at [customerservice@coalision.com](mailto:customerservice@coalision.com) or at 1-800-360-6724 option 5, Monday to Friday from 9AM to 5PM Eastern Time.

### Coalision Europe

Coalision Europe SAS

SIRET : 500 825 419 R.C.S Bayonne

TVA # : FR 07500825419 

44, Rue Luis-Mariano, Biarritz 64200 

Tel : +33 (0)5 47 20 80 02

Email : [saceurope@lolelife.com](mailto:saceurope@lolewomen.com)

Editor: **  Coalision Inc.**

Editorial Manager:  **Coalision Inc.**

Hosting Provider:  **Shopify Inc.**

Web Design:  **Coalision Inc.**
